队长西罗·梅西昨天开始了与海厄利亚市的友谊赛。
Captain Ciro Messi began his friendly fight yesterday against the city of Hialeah.
El capitán Ciro Messi comenzó su pelea amable ayer contra la ciudad de Hialeah.
与国际迈阿密 7 岁以下青训队并肩作战的西罗 (Ciro) 被签为队长，
playing alongside the inter Miami Under-7 Academy team, Ciro who was signed as captain,
jugando junto al equipo inter Miami Under-7 Academy, Ciro quien fue apuntado como capitán,
他在比赛中表现出了极大的热情，其中有一个特别有趣的时刻，那就是Syro收到了对手的滑稽举动。
He showed great enthusiasm during the game, and there was a particularly funny moment when Syro received a funny approach from an opponent.
mostró gran entusiasmo durante el juego, y hubo un momento particularmente divertido cuando Syro recibió un acercamiento divertido de un oponente.
很高兴看到西罗向队友要球，在他们把球传给他后，
It was beautiful to see Siro asking his teammate for the ball, and after they passed it to him,
Fue hermoso ver a Siro pidiendo a su compañero por la bola, y después de que la pasaron a él,
他遇到了对方球员的一些抵抗，西罗似乎摔倒在对方的脚上。
He faced some resistance from the opposing player, and Siro appeared to fall onto the opponent's foot.
Se enfrentó a alguna resistencia del jugador opuesto, y Siro parecía caer sobre el pie del oponente.
结果滑稽地摔倒了，因为他似乎模仿了他父亲的职业风格，同时握住了他的左腿。
resulting in a humorous fall, as he appeared to mimic his father's professional style while holding his left leg.
然而，看看接下来发生的事情，当他的同伴和对手都围住他的时候，赛勒斯很快就站了起来。
However, look what happened next, when both his companions and opponents surrounded him, Cyrus quickly returned to his feet.
Sin embargo, vean lo que sucedió después, cuando ambos sus compañeros y oponentes lo rodearon, Ciro rápidamente regresó a sus pies.
比赛的结局尚不清楚，但从球迷分享的录音来看，
The end of the game is not yet known, but from the recordings shared by fans,
El final de la partida aún no se sabe, pero de las grabaciones compartidas por los fans,
西罗的球队似乎收到了多个目标，其中包括对方球队模仿西罗的父亲莱昂内尔·梅西的庆祝动作。
It appears that Syro's team received several targets, including a celebration from the opposing team miming Syro's father, Lionel Messi.
Parece que el equipo de Syro recibió varios objetivos, incluyendo una celebración del equipo opuesto que mimica al padre de Syro, Lionel Messi.
看看，看看，看看我。
Look, look, look at me.
Mira, mira, mírame.